<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Jun Wang 王珺</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Jun Wang 王珺</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Current Teaching</title>
      <link>https://example.com/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Numerical Analysis Spring 2021, course ID: 60420254  Instructor: Jun Wang, TA: Hao Sun   This course is a one semester course meant to introduce graduate students from science and engineering disciplines to the fundamentals of numerical mathematics. (But any graduate student seriously interested in applied mathematics should take it.) It will be an introductory course covering a broad range of topics such as: interpolation, numerical differentiation, numerical quadrature, linear systems, and least squares problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies</title>
      <link>https://example.com/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>Beyond mathematics In the limited time when I&amp;rsquo;m not doing math, I have a lot of hobbies, which include (but are not restricted to):
 Fine art (Chinese painting, calligraphy, pen and ink drawing, etc.) Literature (poetry, fiction, literary critique) Beijing Opera  If you are an aspiring artist or writer too, welcome to stop by and have a chat! A nonacademic webpage/blog is under construction. Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://example.com/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/home/</guid>
      <description>About Me  Jun Wang
Assistant Professor
Yau Mathematical Sciences Center
Tsinghua University
Contact Jin Chun Yuan West Building, Room 136
Tsinghua University, Beijing, China - 100084
Email: jwang2020 (at) tsinghua.edu.cn
 Research Interest  Fast algorithms. Numerical quadratures. Automatic mesh refinement. Integral equation method for elliptic and parabolic partial differential equations. Numerical methods for the simulation of diffusion and Stokesian flows.  Selected Publications  An adaptive fast Gauss transform in two dimensions, J.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
